Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory9 Mss.B.B61.inventory09
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents M
  - Mus.f. Volkerkunde, Leipzig, 1898 Sept. 1; 1p. (Box 65)
  - Museum of Modern Art (Box 65)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 17; 1p.
  - Museums Collection-Exchange (Box 65)
    See Bastian, A.
  - Museums für Volkerkunde, München (Box 65)
    See Scherman, L.
  - Mussey, Henry Raymond (Box 65)
    - From Boas, 1917 May 2
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Sept. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 20; 1p.
    - (Enc: letter of N. J. Senators), 1929 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 May 8
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept.6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, Dec. 31, 1919; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 28; 1p.
  - Mutch, James S. (Box 65)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1917 July 26
    - To Boas, 1885 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1885 Dec. (?); 6p.
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1886 undated
    - To Boas, 1886 May 8
    - To Boas, 1886 undated
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 28; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 27; 5p.
  - Mutch, Mrs. James S. (Box 65)
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 14
  - Mutch, Jessie A. (Box 65)
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 18; 2p.
  - Mutschmann, N. (Box 65)
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 31; 2p.
  - Mutual Subscription Agency (Box 65)
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 6; 1p.
  - Myer, Edward (Box 65)
    - To Boas, 1912 July 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1915 May 15; 3p.
  - Myers, Alonzo F. (Box 65)
    - From Boas, 1939 July 6; 1p.
  - Myers, C. E. (Box 65)
    - C. E. Myers -- to F.W. Hodge, 1901 Oct. 31
  - Myers, Frederick N. (Box 65)
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 25; 1p.
  - Myers, John C. (Box 65)
    - From Boas, 1930 May 13; 2p.
  - Myers, John T. (Box 65)
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 June 2; 2p.
  - Myrdal, Gunnar (Box 65)
    - To Boas, 1939 June 12; 1p.
  - Myres, John L. (Box 65)
    - From Boas, 1911 May 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 May 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 24; 4p.
    - (Re International Congress of anthropology and prehistoric archaeology), 1931 Feb. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 14; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 13; 1p.